You
Don't you think it's a little too hot to be wearing all of that kick kick we've gone over this before heirs of the night tribe
We're not affected by heat the way mortals are oh
Jeez, it's like walking into a hairdryer. Oh
Oh
Detestable light of the Sun
You have won today's battle, but there shall come a time when the night tribe will fill up the world in darkness and then no more light
Right now I wouldn't object to that
I'm still alive.
Big brother, you must be exhausted.
So nice of you to join us today.
Yeah, just like I always do at this time.
It's summer vacation.
Why would you wait until school would normally be out?
What time did you guys get here?
About one o'clock.
Meat was already here being productive,
playing a video game.
She wasn't that far in.
Yozra showed up just a little after Senna.
So early.
And let me guess, you were here too.
I arrived here at 8 a.m.
It was very important for me to be here before you.
I'd rather take my own life than have you wait.
Don't take this the wrong way, but it's not that big a deal.
I've already prepared your lunch.
Uh, that's sweet, but I ate before I left.
I'm sorry, and there's no reason to cook for me
now that school's out.
Does this mean my services are no longer needed
and you're letting me go?
Heaven help my heart.
My big brother doesn't need me anymore.
I am worthless in his eyes.
I have no choice but to end it all.
I didn't mean it like that.
I need you.
I'm just not hungry.
If you're not going to eat both of those,
can I have one?
I'm starving.
Ugh.
Brilliant timing.
I bet she was expecting me to bring her something.
Look, you saved the day.
Is it cool if I give this to Maria instead?
Not that I wouldn't want it.
I just mean it would help if you made her lunch
instead of me during the summer break to save time.
Um, it would not be appropriate for a samurai
to serve two masters.
I'm sorry.
What is he talking about?
All right, listen.
It's not serving two masters.
Maria's like a sister to me,
so you'd be doing a noble service for your master
if you looked after her, wouldn't you?
Yes, I would.
You're right.
I would actually consider it a great honor, sir.
You mean it?
You see me as your little sister?
Miss Maria,
my big brother has requested
that I prepare your meals for you,
and so I will now be at your service.
I know!
Isn't it great?
Yeah!
Oh!
You got all this stuff from the convenience store?
Oh, look how much sugar's in them!
Yum!
Yeah, this isn't the healthiest meal
you could have brought me.
You're such a strong, healthy man.
I knew you could handle it.
Plus, you deserved a break.
Thank you.
Let's say from here on out
you prepare only nutritious meals for Maria, okay?
I understand.
As you wish.
What's the point in learning good behavior
if you're just going to give the reward away?
See you later.
Have a good day.
Oh, man.
Made it.
Good to see you.
Looks like you've already been working hard.
Hi.
Where is everyone?
I don't know.
They're not here yet.
Miss Maria came by for a little while
and then remembered she had some sisterly duties
to tend to, so she went home.
Okay.
Did you bring her lunch?
Yes.
I made sure it was healthy
just as you instructed.
Very rich in vitamins and calcium.
And protein.
How many protein shakes did she drink?
It wasn't easy to tell you the truth.
She resisted, but they were your order,
so I had no choice but to force them down.
Tell me you're joking.
It reminded me a little of that story
we learned in history class
about the execution of Mampuku Maru.
Mampuku who?
Maru.
He was only ten when his parents abandoned him
thinking he'd be safe from the evil rulers.
Instead, he was found and beheaded.
I bet the way that little boy screamed
when he met his death
sounded just like poor Maria.
What do you mean, scream?
Please, tell me what happened.
She resisted, but they were your order,
so I had no choice but to force them down.
Your orders.
All right, starting tomorrow,
see if you can make something
that's both nutritious and tastes good
to a ten-year-old.
I don't need any more Mampukuru incidents here.
Right.
Your wish is my command.
Oh, man.
Are they ever going to show up?
You've had such a long day, big brother.
You're all here, of course.
Why didn't any of you come yesterday?
Poor Kodaka.
Were you feeling lonely by yourself without Rika?
Lonely is not exactly the word I would use.
Sorry, Kodaka.
Something suddenly came up.
Yeah, and I was too busy being jerked around.
How so?
I thought the game was almost over,
so I was just going to finish it and then leave.
But as it turns out,
I actually had four more hours to go,
way longer than I expected.
I didn't even notice what time it was
because I was lost in the journey.
When Makane finally met her prince at the end,
it was so beautiful, I couldn't move.
You were playing a video game.
It's more than just a game.
You can borrow it.
You'll see.
It's a life-changing experience.
When you finish, you have to start it over.
The ending changes the entire meaning of the beginning
and the whole journey,
you just wouldn't realize it's about how we're all in a...
I just thought of something.
What?
Let's come up with a way that we can let each other know
what time we're all going to be here
and if we can make it or not.
I think you may be onto something there.
I'm surprised that came out of you, Kodaka.
But now that it has, how do we do it?
I was thinking maybe like an internet group or something?
You're crazy.
You won't even consider it?
I try to use the internet as little as possible.
Online shopping and research are about it for me.
Okay, but why?
I did something recently
and I don't want to be recognized.
I'm not even going to ask what that's about.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, I had a pretty crappy experience with message boards
so I'm not interested in being found online.
Just thinking about it pisses me off.
I could kill those ugly trolls for the way they treated me.
They will never be forgiven for the things they said.
What happened?
Did you get in a fight?
I was harassed.
They were calling Natsumi a heartless, lobotomized hooker
just because of the way she looks
and I was not going to let that slide.
I told them looks aren't everything
and she's actually very nice once you get to know her.
And how well do you know her?
Well enough that talking crap about her around me
is pretty much a declaration of war.
They can either admit they were wrong and apologize to me
or we can fight it out
and determine who's right the old-fashioned way.
So what you're saying is message boards
aren't going to work for you, right?
Oh, I know.
How about setting up a page for a private group on Nixie?
What are you doing on Nixie, Kodaka?
And why haven't you added me?
Because I'm not on it, that's why.
You know it?
Yeah.
You're a member, aren't you?
Of course not.
Why would I put myself out there for all those stalkers?
Yeah, I agree.
Rika's not a member yet either.
Turns out it's not the easiest site to join.
You have to actually know someone
and have them add you to their contact list.
So since none of us are members,
we couldn't join if we wanted to.
Nixie isn't the only social networking site, though.
There must be something private
that doesn't require an invitation.
Rika has a suggestion.
Why don't we just exchange phone numbers
and use text messaging?
Texting?
You mean send messages with our cell phones?
Yeah, that's what it is, right?
I guess.
I mean, I forget sometimes
I can text people besides my sister.
Rika, you are a genius!
Text messaging?
I never even thought about that.
The only other thing I used on my phone
was the GPS in some karaoke apps they downloaded.
That does it.
Rika, you leave me no other option
but to agree that you are a genius.
Rika is very thankful for the compliments.
Okay, great, let's do this!
Who's ready to exchange numbers with Rika?
I am.
Okay, here it is.
I'll go get mine.
Come on.
Here it is.
This is my cellular telephone.
The numbers don't just jump in there by themselves.
Oh, yeah, that's a good point.
Rika's never seen one like this.
It's so pretty.
The color almost glows.
Uh, thank you?
Thank you.
Rika sent a group text.
Did you all get it?
You messaged all of us?
I don't have anything.
You sure you sent it?
I didn't get anything either.
Maybe my phone doesn't get them?
Or maybe you have to send it to me separately.
Where would I look for it?
Which picture do I click on?
I'm not seeing anything.
Rika, you might have to send it to me again.
This sucks!
I must have freaking deleted it or something
because it's not in here.
I got it.
How did you do that?
Just reply back and we'll all have yours.
There it is.
Rika has your address now.
And look, it comes with a picture, too.
What's happening?
Why am I having a hard time figuring this out?
Why is it so easy for them?
Because they're from the future.
Kids these days, they're much more advanced.
It's true.
They're growing up in a new virtual generation.
They live their entire lives just like video games
with digital controls.
Somehow a stupid smartphone made us generations ahead of them.
People like Big Brother who are used to doing things
without technology have a hard time understanding
why it's useful and sometimes feel threatened.
How is it that you're so well-versed
in the ways of text messaging?
Why didn't you tell me about this before?
This is dumb.
It doesn't make sense.
And it doesn't make sense for someone
who doesn't have any friends
to use a feature like this.
Screw it.
I'm just going to type in your number the normal way,
so tell me what it is.
I was just thinking the exact same thing.
This is way too much work.
Here, just copy it off my screen.
I'm almost done.
Why is your stupid number so freaking long?
Um, I don't think you have to type in the dashes.
Okay.
Then how am I supposed to type it?
There.
I did it.
Great.
I think I'm going to try it.
You ready?
I'm about to send a text message.
Yeah.
Go.
I think I got it.
Are you sure?
I mean, I did.
This is you, right?
Great.
So now I just have to save your number.
Y-O-Z-O-R-A.
Save.
Sweet, it worked.
Another contact in my phone besides my family.
Hey, this actually feels kind of cool
seeing your name in there.
Are you serious?
You don't have numbers of friends from other schools?
No, is that bad?
It's not like I didn't have friends.
We just always said we'd exchange numbers
when I left, and then we never did.
I guess that makes me kind of a crappy guy, huh?
Uh, maybe.
But on the bright side,
now I get to be your very first phone friend.
And you get to be my very first phone anything.
I don't even have my family's numbers saved.
This is a big deal, Kodaka.
Well, I'm so honored.
Hmm.
Rika was starting to feel really guilty
about not giving better instructions on texting,
but seeing them so elated
after figuring it out on their own
makes Rika think it worked out for the best.
Whatever.
It's just a stupid cell phone.
What's the big deal?
Why are you so angry?
What makes you think I'm angry?
I don't know my mistake.
Hey, what's your number?
I'll type it in now that I know how.
I don't have one.
What?
I don't have a stupid cell phone, okay?
And I don't want one!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that.
Don't be sorry.
I said I don't want one.
They're just props for all the stupid giggly bimbos
in my class who need to feel like they're important.
I'm way too busy being organically awesome
to worry about that.
Well, there are certainly more people in this world
who don't have a cell phone than those who do.
And we manage just fine, thank you.
I'd even be okay if I didn't have a home phone.
But then I'd be depriving way too many people
of hearing this goddess's voice in their ear,
and nobody should miss out on that miracle.
We're all thankful for your mercy.
Hello?
It's me.
Just wanted to double-check if you saved my number.
Yeah, it's still in there.
Come back.
I mean, as long as you're on the phone, let's talk.
But you're right there.
It's different on the phone.
I can ask phone call questions.
So what did you have for dinner last night?
I don't know.
It was good, though.
Really?
That's what you're going to talk about on a cell phone?
Who cares what you had for dinner?
Keep your voice down, Meat.
Can't you see we're on the phone?
I don't want to have to talk all over your squawking.
Now run along and do something jiggly.
This is really convenient, too.
Now we can talk to each other about whatever we want,
even if we're not in the same room.
Then why don't you guys go somewhere and demonstrate?
I'll give you a call when I'm about to leave
so you'll know when I'll be here.
We'll figure out how to group text
and use that to plan
and discuss all the club activities.
I forgot to mention that I went to a great restaurant last night
and ordered meat.
I had a really amazing curry with chicken.
Meat.
If you're wondering how the meat was,
I'd say it was quite tender and delicious.
What are you talking about over there?
Meat.
This has nothing to do with you.
I'm talking about the restaurant's meat.
Chicken.
Meat.
Not the pig.
But meat.
That was marinated perfectly in my curry.
I don't know how they meet the demands
for their meat dishes.
Meat is usually so expensive.
Stop talking about meat!
Shut up, you stupid idiot!
You're such a jerk!
Meat has some lungs in there, doesn't she?
As if you weren't expecting that.
Your talent for pressing Sina's buttons
is both sick and impressive.
Hm.
How's it going?
C-c-c-c-c.
My friend, the night has brought you home.
Yep.
I'm gonna make dinner.
You hungry?
In one click, my contacts have doubled.
Who could be calling at this hour?
Uh, hello?
Was someone just trying to prank me?
Hello?
Anyone there?
Um, hi. Yes.
My name is Senna, and, um, I'm looking for Kodaka.
I mean, is Kodaka there?
Senna, are you okay?
Yeah. Um, is this Kodaka?
Yes.
What's wrong with you, creepypants?
That scared the crap out of me.
Why'd you change your voice like a psychotron?
Are you trying to trick me?
It's how I sound when I'm half asleep.
Do you have any idea what time it is?
I don't have time to discuss your vocal acrobatics right now.
Which cell phone do you have?
The one I've always had.
And which one is that?
What brand? Style? Do you like it?
Why? Don't be a smarty.
Oh.
Well, the company is TurnAU.
I don't know what the model is, though.
Well, go look. I'll wait.
What?
Hurry up!
All right. It's an M61B.
TurnAU, M61B?
That's right.
Okay, got it. Talk to you later.
What the hell was that all about?
Completely naked and waiting for you, Kodaka.
You just imagined Rika naked, didn't you?
You're such a dirty pervy.
Guess that means you'd want to know that Yozara's wearing a flesh suit, too.
Here's a picture of her perfectly soft and round patootie to prove it.
Hope you enjoyed.
I'm wearing clothes, and that was Rika's arm.
Oh, yeah.
Yozara, stop!
Why are you pulling down Rika's undies like that?
No, Rika can't pose like this.
It's too embarrassing.
Kodaka, you need to be careful.
That one's a pervert.
Good to see you.
Rika just discovered how great the girl-on-girl stories are.
Rika never thought about it before, but loves all sexcapades.
They say it's good to have passions in life.
You want some tea?
Sure, thanks.
Where is everyone?
Oh, they all had things to do, so they left.
It's kind of late.
We should get home, too.
Yeah.
The goddess has descended upon you.
Great.
Thanks.
I'm going to sleep.
What?
Really?
That's all you have to say?
Fine.
Let's see how apathetic you are when you see this sexy guy.
You're speechless, aren't you?
I decided to go ahead and ask Daddy for one yesterday, and he bought it for me.
That's the exact same cell phone that I have.
Even the color.
Is it?
What a strange and unplanned coincidence.
There's no way that's a coincidence.
You're so pathetic sometimes.
Now we can text each other and have inside jokes, too.
Quick, get your phone out.
Okay.
Do you know how to send a text so that I can save your number?
Of course I do.
Don't act like you didn't just learn how yesterday.
I wasn't.
Don't be jealous.
I'll let you text me, too.
Here's my number.
I have absolutely no desire to text you.
What?
Not even for the club?
Then why did I buy this stupid thing?
So that you can stalk me, apparently.
Please.
No one wants to deal with you more than they have to.
I was just trying to be a good clubmate.
Not my fault if I send something out and you're completely lost because you are being a droopy mcdrooper.
I wanted to save you some embarrassment.
The least you can do is thank me, God.
Thank you, but I'm fine.
I'll find another way to keep up.
We already tried other ways to keep up.
Aw.
Are we throwing a temper tantrum?
That's not the way to get what you want from me.
Try being a little more grown up and sincere.
What are you saying?
If you think I'm going to beg you, you're crazy.
You know what?
Forget it.
I don't want your smelly number.
She's way too soft, for real.
It's Senna.
I need you to give me that Horn Beast's number.
She's gone too far.
I need to get her back.
This is what she says in her first text message?
I'm not surprised.
If she wants my number that badly, I'll give it to her.
But I need hers first.
What is it, Kotika?
Tell me so I can give her what she wants.
Um, okay.
Help!
I don't know what to do.
This is so awful.
Please.
Can you tell me what happened?
Huh?
It won't stop.
I've tried everything.
Uh.
Whoa.
What is that?
It's so weird.
I think it's broken.
I think I'm going to call it a night.
Kotika, do something.
Uh, well, let me see it.
What am I going to do if it can't be fixed?
It was my first cell phone.
It'll be okay.
We'll fix it.
See, it's already looking better.
I bet if you smile, it'll heal the rest of the way.
Maybe.
Meet, I think everyone these days has a smartphone.
Smartphone? Oh, I've heard of those.
Yeah, they're super efficient and easy to use,
but only under one condition.
You have to be smart to own one.
So I guess you're out of luck there, fatty cakes.
Really?
No, not really, but my God, you're dead.
What? I believed you there for a second, you turd.
But now that I think about it,
it really doesn't make any sense at all.
There's nothing this goddess can't use.
Next time, school swimsuits don't appear.
What? Swimsuit episode?
Why do guys love swimsuits so much?
It just looks like wet underwear.
Theresa, my нев —
This is the real change.
How do we learn, what's anything else?
What...?
Our dernière change.
theme tom in and it's a fun one,
It's a darkplanatory task.
so we can tell them that,
guys, what are your favorite things and finishing?
How do we bring this?
We get this one?
We can see the other thing that we're in Bible study.
You look around.
I'll this person every devil's life,
and as you can talk about this,
it's a fun one.
I just want the person it's way to ask us to help it.
fearful of us to define this scene.
You must show people that like thosemış,
and we look at the demais types of things and tattoos.
We do not recognize a difference,